Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(تَوأَم)
(Episode 23)
(الحلقة 23)
"Zhaoyue Pavilion."
"جناح تشاويو."
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
you truly foresaw it.
لقد توقعت ذلك حقا.
Lu Zhao really did notice something unusual.
لقد لاحظ لو تشاو حقًا شيئًا غير عادي.
I have already reminded her...
لقد ذكّرتها بالفعل...
as you instructed.
كما ارشدت.
She was in charge of the Xuntian Sect for so long.
لقد كانت مسؤولة عن طائفة شونتيان لفترة طويلة.
If she did not notice that Xiao Ren was acting strangely,
إذا لم تلاحظ أن شياو رين كان يتصرف بغرابة،
that would be truly odd.
سيكون ذلك غريبًا حقًا.
Your Highness is wise.
سموكم حكيم.
This is what you wanted.
هذا ما أردته.
Our deal is done.
لقد تمت صفقتنا.
I hope you, Ninth Uncle, will keep your promise.
أتمنى منك يا عمي التاسع أن تحافظ على وعدك.
How do I know if this map is real or fake?
كيف أعرف إذا كانت هذه الخريطة حقيقية أم مزيفة؟
Your wife...
زوجتك...
is naturally sharp and vigilant.
هو حاد الذكاء و يقظ بطبيعته.
Master Xiao, why not tell us...
سيد شياو، لماذا لا تخبرنا...
how you got it?
كيف حصلت عليه؟
Lu Zhao and I are already married.
لو تشاو وأنا متزوجان بالفعل.
Naturally, she keeps nothing from me.
وبطبيعة الحال، فهي لا تخفي عني أي شيء.
What is wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
The Empress Dowager's birthday is approaching.
يقترب عيد ميلاد الإمبراطورة الأرملة .
I have to personally arrange the imperial city's defenses.
يجب علي أن أقوم بترتيب دفاعات المدينة الإمبراطورية بنفسي.
When is a good time for you...
متى يكون الوقت المناسب لك...
to draw up the defense map for my reference?
لرسم خريطة الدفاع للرجوع إليها؟
I have already drawn it.
لقد رسمته بالفعل.
It is on that bookshelf,
إنه على رف الكتب هذا،
in the box on the second row.
في المربع الموجود في الصف الثاني.
Just take it.
فقط خذها.
Sleep a little longer.
النوم لفترة أطول قليلا.
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
Master Xiao is truly heartless.
المعلم شياو هو حقا بلا قلب.
Newly wed,
متزوج حديثا
and yet you can bear...
ولكنك تستطيع أن تتحمل...
to deceive your wife.
لخداع زوجتك.
The deal is done.
تمت الصفقة.
I hope you will not bother me again.
أتمنى أن لا تزعجني مرة أخرى.
Why is Master Xiao in such a hurry?
لماذا السيد شياو في عجلة من أمره؟
To show my gratitude,
لإظهار امتناني،
I have specially prepared...
لقد قمت بإعداد خاص...
a surprise for you.
مفاجأة لك.
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Naturally, to conspire with me...
بطبيعة الحال، للتآمر معي...
in a grand design.
في تصميم كبير.
I will not believe...
لن أصدق...
a single word he says.
كلمة واحدة يقولها
I know.
أنا أعرف.
There must be something you cannot tell me.
لا بد أن هناك شيئًا لا يمكنك إخباري به.
As long as you tell me the truth,
طالما أنك تقول لي الحقيقة،
even if it is a tiger's den,
حتى لو كان عرين نمر،
I will fight my way out with you.
سأقاتل من أجل الخروج معك.
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
I will explain it to you when we get back.
سأشرح لك ذلك عندما نعود.
We have to get out of here now.
علينا أن نخرج من هنا الآن.
The show has not even begun yet.
العرض لم يبدأ بعد
How can...
كيف يمكن...
the main characters leave early?
الشخصيات الرئيسية تغادر مبكرا؟
Watch out!
احذر!
Situ Xing Yuan.
الموقع شينغ يوان.
You are going back on your word!
أنت تتراجع عن كلمتك!
I never promised...
لم أعد أبدا...
to let you get away unscathed.
لكي أسمح لك بالخروج دون أن يصاب أحد بأذى.
Xiao Ren.
شياو رن.
At a time like this,
في وقت كهذا،
you still refuse to tell me what happened.
مازلت ترفض أن تخبرني بما حدث.
I am afraid he does not have the courage to tell you the truth.
أخشى أنه لا يملك الشجاعة ليخبرك الحقيقة.
Then perhaps I should speak in his stead.
ثم ربما ينبغي لي أن أتحدث نيابة عنه.
Shut up!
اسكت!
Xiao Ren.
شياو رن.
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
I...
أنا...
I am...
أنا أكون...
the son of Song Lou.
ابن سونغ لو.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Before we got married,
قبل أن نتزوج،
were you in a daze...
هل كنت في حالة ذهول؟
because of this?
بسبب هذا؟
Yes.
نعم.
So,
لذا،
you knew about your true identity all along,
لقد كنت تعرف هويتك الحقيقية منذ البداية،
but you deliberately hid it...
ولكنك أخفيته عمدا...
to trick me into marrying you.
لتخدعني للزواج منك.
Yes.
نعم.
You compromised with Situ Xing Yuan...
لقد توصلت إلى تسوية مع سيتو شينغ يوان...
and tricked me into drawing the defense map.
وخدعني في رسم خريطة الدفاع.
I am sorry.
أنا آسف.
Why?
لماذا؟
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
I want to be with you.
أريد أن أكون معك.
Lu Zhao, I want to be with you forever.
لو تشاو، أريد أن أكون معك إلى الأبد.
I want to grow old with you.
أريد أن أكبر معك.
You coward.
أيها الجبان.
You betrayed me in the name of love.
لقد خنتني بإسم الحب.
You colluded with the one who killed me.
لقد تواطأت مع الشخص الذي قتلني.
You do not deserve to be my husband!
أنت لا تستحق أن تكون زوجي!
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
Do you really...
هل حقا...
want to kill me?
تريد قتلي؟
Yes!
نعم!
As the Xuntian Sect leader,
بصفته زعيم طائفة شونتيان،
you secretly conspired with the wicked.
لقد تآمرت سراً مع الأشرار.
That is treachery.
هذه خيانة.
You aided evil,
لقد ساعدت الشر،
disregarding the people's lives.
متجاهلين أرواح الناس.
That is inhumanity.
هذا هو عدم الإنسانية.
My father raised you to adulthood.
لقد ربّاك والدي حتى أصبحت راشداً.
His true heart...
قلبه الحقيقي...
was fed to a wolf.
تم إطعامها إلى الذئب.
That is unfilial.
هذا غير صالح.
You and I swore...
لقد أقسمنا أنا وأنت...
never to betray each other in this life.
لا نخون بعضنا البعض أبدًا في هذه الحياة.
Yet you broke your vow.
ولكنك نقضت عهدك.
That is...
إنه...
unfaithfulness.
خيانة.
Do you really...
هل حقا...
hate me that much?
تكرهني إلى هذه الدرجة؟
We...
نحن...
are...
نكون...
mortal...
بشري...
enemies.
الأعداء.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
It is time.
لقد حان الوقت.
It is your turn to take charge.
الآن دورك لتتولى المسؤولية.
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
I was right about you.
لقد كنت على حق بشأنك.
I knew you would not disappoint me.
لقد عرفت أنك لن تخيب ظني.
Situ Xing Yuan.
الموقع شينغ يوان.
You heartless beast!
أيها الوحش عديم القلب!
I will kill you sooner or later!
سأقتلك عاجلا أم آجلا!
Be patient.
كن صبوراً.
The days ahead are long.
الأيام القادمة طويلة.
When I return victoriously,
عندما أعود منتصرا،
I will have...
سوف يكون لدي...
a heart-to-heart talk with you.
محادثة من القلب إلى القلب معك.
Stop!
قف!
Situ Xing Yuan!
الموقع شينغ يوان!
Do you dare...
هل تجرؤ...
fight me to the death today?
قاتلني حتى الموت اليوم؟
Stop!
قف!
Stop! Situ Xing Yuan!
توقف! سيتو شينغ يوان!
Stop right there, you animal!
توقف هنا، أيها الحيوان!
You animal!
يا حيوان!
Get up now.
استيقظ الآن.
Come on, tomorrow is the wedding.
هيا، غدا هو حفل الزفاف.
We still have a lot to prepare.
لا زال أمامنا الكثير للتحضير.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
You have been busy lately.
لقد كنت مشغولاً في الآونة الأخيرة.
If it is because...
إذا كان ذلك بسبب...
of the vow you made to Father when you were young,
من النذر الذي قطعته لأبيك عندما كنت صغيرًا،
you do not have to blame yourself.
لا يتوجب عليك إلقاء اللوم على نفسك.
You did not go against Father's wish.
لم تذهب ضد رغبة الأب.
You have done a great job protecting...
لقد قمت بعمل عظيم في حماية...
the Xuntian Sect and me.
طائفة شونتيان وأنا.
Did we not agree?
هل لم نتفق؟
We will not be siblings anymore.
لن نكون أشقاء بعد الآن.
Since we are husband and wife,
بما أننا زوج وزوجة،
come hell...
تعال الجحيم...
or high water,
أو ارتفاع منسوب المياه،
we shall face it together.
سوف نواجهها معًا.
If you have something to say, say it.
إذا كان لديك شيء لتقوله، قل ذلك.
I am here with you.
انا هنا معك.
I am the son...
أنا الابن...
of the traitor Song Lou.
الخائن سونغ لو.
of Southern Qing's traitor,
من خائن جنوب تشينغ،
the Xiao family's sworn enemy,
العدو اللدود لعائلة شياو،
Song Lou's...
سونغ لو...
only legitimate son.
الابن الشرعي الوحيد.
(Song Family Genealogy)
(علم الأنساب لعائلة سونغ)
Since you knew about it long ago,
بما أنك عرفت ذلك منذ زمن طويل،
why are you only telling me now?
لماذا تخبرني الآن فقط؟
Because I cannot bear to let you go.
لأنني لا أستطيع أن أتحمل تركك.